I'm a fortune will be I am
My own dog, my own fricking baby
My own old lady on the floor
The types in glittery decor
Unfortunately I take care
I still fell walk in every day
I hand my legs to the feet
I give my hand to the leash
Every other day I'm wondering
What's a human being gotta be like?
What's a way to just be competent?
Is sweet instincts ruined my life?
Every other day I'm wondering
Was it a mistake to try and define?
What I'm certain's mad in competence?
Is sweet instincts ruined my life?
I can't smell the words all the time
Not case through eight, no K-9
For human grossly underqualified
For K-9 grossly overqualified
I don't blend in pet smart
And that truth remains for the wrong man
Cause in either case they say to me
What the fuck is a loss of miles three?
Every other day I'm wondering
What's a human being gotta be like?
What's a way to just be competent?
Is sweet instincts ruined my life?
Every other day I'm wondering
Was it a mistake to try and define?
What I'm certain's mad in competence?
Is sweet instincts ruined my life?
Every other day I'm wondering
Was it a mistake to try and define?
Just watch me
Nobody even goes my name
No one suspects that I'm not finding
Nobody I was behavioral frank and Stein
Just look out Victor and I live
Instead with the wire you were there
And all the majors at the labels
Reboot it soon as I am able
Every other day I'm wondering
What's a human being gotta be like?
What's a way to just be competent?
Is sweet instincts ruined my life?
Every other day I'm wondering
Was it a mistake to try and define?
What I'm certain's mad in competence?
Is sweet instincts ruined my life?
Every other day I'm wondering
Was it a mistake to try and define?
What I'm certain's mad in competence?
Sweet instincts ruined my life
Attached to competence we've now reached our destination
We're only enjoying the flight and having our stay